https://www.regent.edu/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Regent University / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Regent University understands that our users are concerned about submitting personal information either through our website or other means. Our users’ individual privacy rights are important to us. For this reason, we provide this explanation of our data handling practices.
Our privacy guidelines are solely governed by Virginia statutes including, but not limited to, the Virginia Privacy Protection Act of 1976, the Virginia Freedom of Information Act, and any and all applicable federal legislation.
This notice in no manner serves to represent a contract between Regent University and (you) the reader or any person who submits, in any form, information to Regent University.
How We Gather Information
Here at Regent University, we have many ways that our users can submit data to us. One of the most convenient ways is to complete a web form. These forms collect information from our users and send it to the proper recipient within Regent University. In addition, we also collect information via other means such as electronic mail (Email), telephone calls, and postal mail.
While using the Internet to connect to Regent University, some technical information is automatically collected for statistical reference. Though these items may not necessarily identify an individual, we want our users to know that this information is recorded without any causal action on their behalf. These items are as follows:
The Internet address (IP address) of the machine our users are using to connect to www.regent.edu. This may also produce a coordinating host and domain name for our users’ computers.
The type of Internet Browser our users are using to connect to www.regent.edu. Also, the pages our users are requesting from our site.
The site from which our users immediately left when visiting www.regent.edu. Also, any ‘cookie’ related information as described in this notice.
What are [Internet Browser] ‘Cookies’?
Cookies are files that exist on client computers that contain information to help us better serve our users’ needs. They may help us to remember customized settings so that each time a user returns to www.regent.edu, we create a custom view just for that user. For our users’ personal security, browsers have settings that allow each user to control how cookies are stored and when and how they are removed. Any information gained from cookies is governed by the same guidelines as information our users purposely submit to Regent University.
Internet Browser “Do Not Track” Feature
Some browsers incorporate a “Do Not Track” (DNT) feature that, when activated, signals to websites that you do not want to be tracked. Because there is not yet an accepted standard for how to respond to browser DNT signals, we do not currently respond to them.
How We Use Information
Information we gain from any person is used for official Regent University purposes only. We do not share, sell, or loan data to any organization for purposes not relating to our direct efforts. There are times that we may share data to meet federal regulations, to facilitate large campaigns, comply with law enforcement, or distribute special offers to our users. As such, no user should have any reasonable expectation of absolute privacy (see our Acceptable Use Policy for further guidance). In the course of general business, employees and partner’s employees will have access to data our users submit. For this reason, we take precautions to ensure that we protect our users’ data while in our control or while in the control of one of our campaign partners.
Your Information, Your Choice
Because our users’ information belongs to them and can individually identify each one of them, we remind our users that they are not required to share such information with Regent University. In doing so, our users will still be able to freely navigate our website without submitting any information to us. However, if a user desires to purchase items, apply for employment, apply for admission, or any other service which requires us to collect information, that user must submit in some manner his/her information to us. Should that user not provide in full the requested information, he/she may not be eligible to receive his/her requested service.
Our Commitment to Data Security
At Regent University we utilize considerable security protections in order to collect and protect users’ information. Where necessary, we employ Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) in order to facilitate an encrypted connection between the user’s computer and our web server. We encourage our users to become familiar with secure means by which to submit information to Regent University. Our users should understand that Email is an insecure medium and that we discourage transmission of personally identifiable information via this means. In order to protect the data we store and to ensure our users’ privacy is safeguarded, we employ numerous security controls, follow secure processes, and execute internal audit procedures. Our users’ confidential information and personal privacy is of utmost importance to us. We strive to protect our users’ information in a manner consistent with the laws and regulations of the state of Virginia and with all applicable federal legislation.
Take the Next Step
Visit Campus
Apply Now
Request Information
